Guide to the Anson Phelps Stokes Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence of Anson Phelps Stokes, 1879-(1892-1958); PART I. I; 57.5 linear feet (139 boxes)
  - General Correspondence, 1922-1930 May 31
    - Roy, L. A., 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 41, Folder 680-687)
    - Ruml, Beardsley, 1922-1929 (Box 41, Folder 688)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 9/24
    - Russian refugee relief
      See: Part I, box 182, folders 193-202
    - Russia, religious persecution in, 1930 March (Box 41, Folder 689)
    - Sa-Schm, 1922-1926 March 15 (Box 41, Folder 690-692)
    - Sa-Schm, 1926 March 16 -1930 May 31 (Box 42, Folder 693-695)
    - St. Anna's Church Home, 1928 March - 1929 July (Box 42, Folder 696)
    - St. Anna's Church Home, 1929 October - 1930 May (Box 42, Folder 697)
    - St. Paul's School, Concord, N.H.
      See: Part I, box 183, folders 215-227
    - Sakai, Barnabas T., 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 42, Folder 698)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 3/8
    - Schieffelin, Dr. William Jay, 1922-1925 (Box 42, Folder 699)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 13/19
    - Schieffelin, Dr. William Jay, 1926 January 1 - 1930 May 31 (Box 42, Folder 700)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 10/8
    - Schn-Se, 1922 - 1930 May 31 (Box 42, Folder 701-706)
    - Sf-Sl, 1922-1925 September 15 (Box 42, Folder 707-709)
    - Sf-Si, 1925 September 16 -1930 May 30 (Box 43, Folder 710-714)
    - Sibley, James L., 1922-1926 (Box 43, Folder 715)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 28/29
    - Sibley, James L., 1928 January 1 - 1929 July 31 (Box 43, Folder 716)
    - Slade, Francis Louis, 1922 - 1930 May 31 (Box 43, Folder 717)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 29/38
    - Sm, 1922 -1930 May 31 (Box 43, Folder 718-722)
    - Smuts, General J. C., Union of S. Africa, 1929 December - 1930 February (Box 43, Folder 724)
    - Sn-Ss, 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 43, Folder 725-729)
    - St-Sz, 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 730-735)
    - (U.S.) State Department, 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 736)
    - Stewart & Shearer, 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 737)
    - Stimson, Henry L., 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 738)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 5/8
    - Street, Elwood, 1929 January 1 - 1930 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 739)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 24/16
    - Ta-Tg, 1922 - 1930 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 740-743)
    - Taft, William Howard, 1922-1925 December 31 (Box 44, Folder 744)
    - Taft, William Howard, 1926 January 1 - 1930 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 745)
    - Th, 1922 - 1930 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 746-750)
    - Thorne, Samuel, 1922 - 1924 October 31 (Box 44, Folder 751)
    - Thorne, Samuel, 1925 January 1 - 1926 December 31 (Box 44, Folder 752)
    - Thorne, Samuel, 1927 January 1 - 1928 December 31 (Box 44, Folder 753)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 12/19
    - Thorne, Samuel, 1929 January 1 - 1930 May 31 (Box 44, Folder 754)
    - Ti-Tz, 1922 - 1930 May 31 (Box 45, Folder 755-760)
    - Tuskegee Institute, 1925-1928 (Box 45, Folder 761-762)
    - U, 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 45, Folder 763-768)
    - V, 1922 - 1927 July 15 (Box 45, Folder 769-772)
    - V, 1927 July 16 - 1930 May 31 (Box 46, Folder 773-774)
    - Vreeland, Herbert H., 1922-1924 October 31; 1928 (Box 46, Folder 775)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 35/32
    - Wa-Wd, 1922-1929 December 31 (Box 46, Folder 776-783)
    - Wa-Wd, 1930 May 31 (Box 46, Folder 784)
    - Washington Cathedral
    - Washington Loan and Trust Company, 1926 March 16 - 1930 May 31 (Box 46, Folder 785-787)
    - We-Wh, 1922 - 1927 July 15 (Box 46, Folder 788-791)
    - We-Wh, 1927 July 16-1930 May 31 (Box 47, Folder 792-793)
    - Wellington, Rosamund B., 1922-1924 October 31 (Box 47, Folder 794)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 13/5
    - Welch, Lewis S. & Thompson, Bryson F., 1922-1928 December 31 (Box 47, Folder 795-797)
    - Welch, Lewis S. Insurance, 1929 January 1 - 1930 May 31 (Box 47, Folder 798)
    - Wi-Wn, 1922 - 1930 May 31 (Box 47, Folder 799-804)
    - Winslow, Lanier & Company, 1929 January 1 - 1930 May 31 (Box 47, Folder 805)
    - Wo-Wz, 1922 - 1930 May 31 (Box 48, Folder 806-811)
    - Woodson, Carter G., 1922 - 1930 May 31 (Box 48, Folder 812)
    - Work, Monroe N., 1925 January 1 - 1926 June 30 (Box 48, Folder 813)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 8/9
    - Work, Monroe N., 1926 July 1 - December 31 (Box 48, Folder 814)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 9/10
    - Work, Monroe N., 1927 January 1 - 1928 January 31 (Box 48, Folder 815)
    - Work, Monroe N., 1928 February 1 - 1930 May 31 (Box 48, Folder 816)
    - Wyckoff, J. Edwards, 1927 December 1 - 1930 May 31 (Box 48, Folder 817-819)
    - X-Y-Z, 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 48, Folder 820-825)
    - Yale University & Yale Associations, 1922-1930 May 31 (Box 48, Folder 826)
  - General Correspondence, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31
    - Aa-Am, 1930 June 1 -1939 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 828-835)
    - Alexander, Will W., 1931 February 9 - 1939 April (Box 49, Folder 835A)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 26/37
    - Letters from persons who received a copy of Stokes's African report, 1934.
      See: Part I, box 175, folder 10
    - An-Az, 1930 June 1 -1935 December 31 (Box 49, Folder 836-841)
    - An-Az, 1936 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 842-843)
    - Anderson, Marian, 1939 January - 1940 May (Box 50, Folder 844)
    - Arnett, Trevor, 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 845)
    - Arnett, Trevor, 1932 January 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 50, Folder 846)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 19/17
    - Arnett, Trevor, 1934 March 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 847)
    - Ba-Bd, 1930 June 1 - 1931 October 31; 1932 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 50, Folder 848-852)
    - Be-Bh, 1930 June 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 50, Folder 853-854)
    - Be-Bh, 1934 March 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 51, Folder 855-857)
    - Beers, Clifford W., 1930 January 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 51, Folder 858)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 13/8
    - Beers, Clifford W., 1932 January 1 - 1934 December 31 (Box 51, Folder 859)
    - Beers, Clifford W., 1935 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 51, Folder 860)
    - Bell, Dr. Bernard I., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 51, Folder 861)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 23/16
    - Bi-Bn, 1930 June 1 -1939 December 31 (Box 51, Folder 862-866)
    - Bo-Bq, 1930 June 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 51, Folder 867-869)
    - Bo-Bq, 1936 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 52, Folder 870-871)
    - Br-Bt, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 52, Folder 872-884)
    - Bratenahl, The Very Rev. G.C.F., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 885)
    - Bratenahl, The Very Rev. G.C.F., 1932 January 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 53, Folder 886)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 6/8
    - Bratenahl, The Very Rev. G.C.F., 1934 March 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 887)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 4/23
    - Bratenahl, The Very Rev. G.C.F., 1936 January 1 - 1937 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 888)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 2/6
    - Brawley, Benjamin, 1930 January 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 889)
    - Brawley, Benjamin, 1934 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 890)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 24/27
    - Breen, Margaret J., 1930 June 1 - 1934 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 891)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 28/42
    - Breen, Margaret J., 1935 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 892)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 19/32
    - Brierley, W.W., 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 893)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 8/8
    - The Brookings Institution
      See: Part I, box 175, folders 11-20
    - Brookings Robert S. & Isabel V., 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 894)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 12/20
    - Brown, Harry W., Jr., 1930 June 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 895)
    - Brown, Helen Gilman (Mrs. Wm. Adams), 1930 June 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 896)
    - Brown, Helen Gilman (Mrs. Wm. Adams), 1934 January 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 897)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 11/13
    - Brown, Helen Gilman (Mrs. Wm. Adams), 1936 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 898)
    - Bu-Bz, 1930 June 1 - 1937 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 899-902)
    - Bu-Bz, 1938 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 903)
    - Phelps-Stokes Fund Dinner in honor of Ralph J. Bunche
      See: Part I, box 180, folders 157-158
    - Burroughs, Nannie H., 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 53, Folder 904)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 7/10
    - Ca-Cg, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 54, Folder 905-914)
    - Campbell, E. Fay, 1930 June 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 54, Folder 915-916)
    - Cassell lawsuit, 1936-1937, 1939 (Box 54, Folder 917)
    - Central China College, 1930 January - 1932, 1934 - 1936 (Box 55, Folder 918-922)
    - Ch-Cn, 1930 June 1 - 1936 December 31 (Box 55, Folder 923-932)
    - Ch-Cn, 1937 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 56, Folder 932a-936)
    - Coa-Coq, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 56, Folder 937-945)
    - Re: Colburn, 1933 October - 1939 December 31 (Box 56, Folder 946-948)
    - The Community Chest of Washington, D.C., 1930 June 1 - 1938 December 31 (Box 57, Folder 949-952)
    - Connelly, A.S., 1931-1937 (Box 57, Folder 953)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 39/17
    - Connely, Willard, 1930 June 1 - 1938 December 31 (Box 57, Folder 954)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 15/18
    - Thomas Cook & Son Travel Service, 1930 June 1 - 1933 May 30 (Box 57, Folder 955-956)
    - Cor-Cz, 190 June 1 - 1936 December 31 (Box 57, Folder 957-963)
    - Cor-Cz, 1937 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 58, Folder 964-966)
    - Da-Dn, 1930 June 1 - 1936 December 31 (Box 58, Folder 967-978)
    - Da-Dn, 1937 January 1 -1939 December 31 (Box 59, Folder 979-982)
    - Darby, Dr. William L., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 59, Folder 983)
    - Darby, Dr. William L., 1932 January 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 59, Folder 984)
    - Darby, Dr. William L., 1934 March 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 59, Folder 985)
    - Deletorsky, Lucy, correspondence re:, 1935 January 1 - 1936 December 31 (Box 59, Folder 986)
    - Deletorsky, Lucy, correspondence re:, 1937 January 1 - December 31 (Box 59, Folder 987)
    - DeVries, Canon W.L., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 59, Folder 988)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 15/13
    - DeVries, Canon W.L., 1932 January 1 (Box 59, Folder 989)
    - DeVries, Canon W.L., 1934 March 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 59, Folder 990)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 8/14
    - DeVries, Canon W.L, 1936 January 1 - 1937 December 31 (Box 59, Folder 991)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 4/3
    - Do-Dz, 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 59, Folder 992)
    - DuBois, W.E.B.
      Letters To APS/From APS: 0/1
    - Do-Dz, 1932 January 1 - December 31 (Box 59, Folder 993)
    - DuBois, W.E.B.
    - Do-Dz, 1933 January 1 - December 31 (Box 59, Folder 994)
    - DuBois, W.E.B.
    - Do-Dz, 1934 January 1 - December 31 (Box 59, Folder 995)
    - Do-Dz, 1935 January 1 - December 31 (Box 59, Folder 996)
    - DuBois, W.E.B.
      Letters To APS/From APS: 3/3
    - Do-Dz, 1936 January 1 - December 31 (Box 59, Folder 997)
    - DuBois, W.E.B.
      Letters To APS/From APS: 3/4
    - Do-Dz, 1937 January 1 - December 31 (Box 60, Folder 998)
    - DuBois, W.E.B.
    - Do-Dz, 1938 January 1 - December 31 (Box 60, Folder 999)
    - DuBois, W.E.B.
      Letters To APS/From APS: 2/7
    - Do-Dz, 1939 January 1 - December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1000)
    - DuBois, W.E.B.
    - Dodge, Clarence Phelps & Regina, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1001)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 21/59
    - Duggan, Dr. Stephen P., 1930 June 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1002)
    - Duggan, Dr. Stephen P., 1934 January 1 - 1936 December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1003)
    - Duggan, Dr. Stephen P., 1937 January 1 - December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1004)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 10/15
    - Duggan, Dr. Stephen P., 1938 January 1 - December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1005)
    - Duggan, Dr. Stephen P., 1939 January 1 - December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1006)
    - E, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1007-1014)
    - Mischa Elman Refugee Benefit Concert, correspondence re:, 1939 March 30 (Box 60, Folder 1015)
    - Embree, Edwin R., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1016)
    - Embree, Edwin R., 1932 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 60, Folder 1017)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 8/19
    - Encyclopedia of the Negro
      See: Part I, box 179, folders 130-136 See: Part I, box 180, folders 137-145
    - Fa-Fn, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 61, Folder 1018-1032)
    - Fawcett, Mr. & Mrs. J. Waldo, 1930 June 1 - December 31 (Box 62, Folder 1033)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 28/25
    - Fawcett, Mr. & Mrs. J. Waldo, 1931 January 1 - June 30 (Box 62, Folder 1034)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 32/20
    - Fawcett, Mr. & Mrs. J. Waldo, 1931 July 1 - December 31 (Box 62, Folder 1035)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 34/16
    - Fawcett, Mr. & Mrs. J. Waldo, 1932 January 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 62, Folder 1036)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 21/14
    - Fawcett, Mr. & Mrs. J. Waldo, 1934 March 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 62, Folder 1037)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 11/16
    - Fiduciary Trust Company of New York, 1934 March 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 62, Folder 1038-1042)
    - Flint, Dr. Joseph M., 1930 June 1 - December 31 (Box 62, Folder 1043)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 18/12
    - Flint, Dr. Joseph M., 1931 January 1 - December 31 (Box 62, Folder 1044)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 14/18
    - Flint, Dr. Joseph M., 1932 January 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 62, Folder 1045)
    - Flint, Dr. Joseph M., 1934 March 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 62, Folder 1046)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 0/6
    - Fo-Fz, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 63, Folder 1047-1053)
    - Ford, James M., 1932 January 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 63, Folder 1054)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 16/14
    - Ford, James M., 1934 March 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 63, Folder 1055)
    - Freeman, Rt. Rev. James E., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 63, Folder 1056)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 13/32
    - Freeman, Rt. Rev. James E., 1932 January 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 63, Folder 1057)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 10/24
    - Freeman, Rt. Rev. James E., 1934 March 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 63, Folder 1058)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 19/47
    - Freeman, Rt. Rev. James E., 1936 January 1 - 1937 December 31 (Box 63, Folder 1059)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 19/43
    - Freeman, Rt. Rev. James E., 1938 January 1 - 1939 June 31 (Box 63, Folder 1060)
    - Ga-Gn, 1930 June 1-1933 December 31 (Box 63, Folder 1061-1063)
    - Ga-Gn, 1934 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 64, Folder 1064-1070)
    - Go-Gz, 1930 June 1 - 1934 December 31 (Box 64, Folder 1071-1076)
    - Go-Gz, 1935 January 1 -1939 December 31 (Box 65, Folder 1077-1084)
    - Gollock, Georgina A., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 65, Folder 1085)
    - Gollock, Georgina A., 1932 January 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 65, Folder 1086)
    - Gollock, Georgina A., 1934 January 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 65, Folder 1087)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 14/25
    - Gollock, Georgina A., 1936 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 65, Folder 1088)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 14/19
    - Gragg, Jeanne Fuller, 1938 January 1 - December 31 (Box 65, Folder 1089)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 15/4
    - Gragg, Jeanne Fuller, 1939 January 1 - December 31 (Box 65, Folder 1090)
    - Grant, Lt. Col. U.S. 3rd, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 65, Folder 1091)
    - Haa-Haq, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 66, Folder 1092-1096)
    - Hansen, Inga M., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 66, Folder 1097)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 12/8
    - Hansen, Inga M., 1932 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 66, Folder 1098)
    - Har-Haz, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 66, Folder 1099-1103)
    - Haynes, Dr. George E. (includes Harmon Award correspondence), 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 66, Folder 1104)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 5/5
    - Haynes, Dr. George E., 1932 January 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 66, Folder 1105)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 4/5
    - Haynes, Dr. George E., 1938 (Box 66, Folder 1106)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 1/4
    - He-Hn, 1930 June 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 66, Folder 1107-1108)
    - He-Hn, 1934 March 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 67, Folder 1109-1111)
    - Ho-Ht, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 67, Folder 1112-1123)
    - Hoffman, Helen Duey, 1937 July 1 - December 31 (Box 67, Folder 1124)
    - Hoffman, Helen Duey, 1938 January 1 - May 31 (Box 67, Folder 1125)
    - Hoffman, Helen Duey, 1938 June 1 - December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1126)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 15/9
    - Hoffman, Helen Duey, 1939 January 1 - December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1127)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 27/11
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1128)
    - Hu-Hz, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1129-1133)
    - Hume, Dr. Edward H., 1930 June 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1134)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 20/13
    - Hume, Dr. Edward H., 1934 January 1 - 1936 December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1135)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 5/4
    - Hume, Dr. Edward H., 1938 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1136)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 3/6
    - Hutchins, Francis S., 1930 June 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1137)
    - Hutchins, Francis S., 1934 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1138)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 22/17
    - I, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 68, Folder 1139-1143)
    - Ihlder, John, 1930 November 1 - 1932 December 31 (Box 69, Folder 1144)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 9/4
    - Ihlder, John, 1933 January 1 - December 31 (Box 69, Folder 1145)
    - Ihlder, John, 1934 January 1 - May 31 (Box 69, Folder 1146)
    - Ihlder, John, 1934 June 1 - December 31 (Box 69, Folder 1147)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 21/12
    - Ihlder, John, 1935 January 1 - 1936 December 31 (Box 69, Folder 1148)
    - Ihlder, John, 1937 January 1 - December 31 (Box 69, Folder 1149)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 12/12
    - Ihlder, John, 1938 January 1 - December 31 (Box 69, Folder 1150)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 16/26
    - Ihlder, John, 1939 January 1 - December 31 (Box 69, Folder 1151)
    - Indian Rights Association, Department of the Interior, and Bureau of Indian Affairs, correspondence with Thomas Jesse Jones and Anson Phelps Stokes re: proposed study of the Navajos sponsored by the Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1938 (Box 69, Folder 1152)
    - Interracial Committee correspondence
      General
      See: Part I, box 189, folders 344-348
    - J, 1930 June 1 - 1937 December 31 (Box 69, Folder 1153-1160)
    - J, 1938 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 70, Folder 1161-1162)
    - Jennings, Coleman, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 70, Folder 1163)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 21/34
    - Johnson, Dr. Mordecai W., 1930 June 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 70, Folder 1164)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 16/15
    - Johnson, Dr. Mordecai W., 1934 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 70, Folder 1165)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 23/27
    - Jones, Dr. Rheinallt, 1932-1939 (Box 70, Folder 1166)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 22/26
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1930 June 1 - 1931 June 30 (Box 70, Folder 1167)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 51/43
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1931 July 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 70, Folder 1168)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 27/25
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1932 January 1 - June 30 (Box 70, Folder 1169)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 42/34
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1932 July 1 - December 31 (Box 70, Folder 1170)
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1933 January 1 - June 30 (Box 70, Folder 1171)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 20/19
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1933 July 1 - December 31 (Box 71, Folder 1172)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 32/33
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1934 January 1 - June 30 (Box 71, Folder 1173)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 29/32
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1934 July 1 - December 31 (Box 71, Folder 1174)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 33/27
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1935 January 1 - February 28 (Box 71, Folder 1175)
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1935 March 1 - May 31 (Box 71, Folder 1176)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 30/27
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1935 June 1 - August 31 (Box 71, Folder 1177)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 29/28
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1935 September 1 - December 31 (Box 71, Folder 1178)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 27/24
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1936 January 1 - May 31 (Box 71, Folder 1179)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 27/29
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1936 June 1 - December 31 (Box 71, Folder 1180)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 21/16
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1937 January 1 - December 31 (Box 71, Folder 1181)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 40/28
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1938 January 1 - June 30 (Box 71, Folder 1182)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 26/18
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1938 July 1 - December 31 (Box 71, Folder 1183)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 25/23
    - Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse, 1939 January 1 - December 31 (Box 71, Folder 1184)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 35/21
    - Ka-Kh, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 1185-1190)
    - Keppel, Frederick P., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 1191)
    - Keppel, Frederick P., 1932 January 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 1192)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 21/30
    - Keppel, Frederick P., 1934 January 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 1193)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 18/27
    - Keppel, Frederick P., 1936 January 1 - 1937 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 1194)
    - Keppel, Frederick P., 1938 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 1195)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 7/11
    - Ki-Kz, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 1196-1200)
    - Krans, Horatio S., 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 72, Folder 1201)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 13/16
    - La-Ld, 1930 June 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 73, Folder 1202-1206)
    - Le-Ln, 1930 June 1 - 1937 December 31 (Box 73, Folder 1207-1215)
    - Le-Ln, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 1216)
    - Le-Ln, 1939 (Box 74, Folder 1217)
    - Lenox School re: gift books to library from Yale University Press in name of Anson Phelps Stokes
      See: George Parmly Day, Part I, box 17, folders 260-264
    - Lewis, Burdette, correspondence and clippings re: Lewis report on relief in Washington, D.C., 1938 January - 1939 January (Box 74, Folder 1218)
    - Lewis, Edwin N., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 74, Folder 1219)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 18/25
    - Lewis, Edwin N., 1932 January 1 - 1934 February 28 (Box 74, Folder 1220)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 31/34
    - Lewis, Edwin N., 1934 March 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 74, Folder 1221)
    - Lewis, Edwin N., 1936 January 1 - 1937 December 31 (Box 74, Folder 1222)
    - Lewis, Edwin N., 1938 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 74, Folder 1223)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 18/17
    - Life Extension Institute, 1930 June 1 - 1936 January 2 (Box 74, Folder 1224)
    - Lindley, correspondence re: proposed biography, 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 74, Folder 1225)
    - Lindley, 1930-1939 (Box 74, Folder 1226)
    - Lo-Lz, 1930 June 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 74, Folder 1227-1229)
    - Lo-Lz, 1934 January 1 - 1939 December 31 (Box 75, Folder 1230-1235)
    - Loram, Dr. C.T., 1930 June 1 - 1931 December 31 (Box 75, Folder 1236)
    - Loram, Dr. C.T., 1932 January 1 - 1933 December 31 (Box 75, Folder 1237)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 34/35
    - Loram, Dr. C.T., 1934 January 1 - 1935 December 31 (Box 75, Folder 1238)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 39/38
    - Loram, Dr. C.T., 1936 January 1 - 1937 December 31 (Box 75, Folder 1239)
      Letters To APS/From APS: 22/24